fastagain.com 2014-09-20

# FastAgain PC Booster | Boost PC Speed & Fix Windows Errors

## Privacy Policy

FastAgain PC Booster SOFTWARE IS DEDICATED TO MAINTAINING THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, AND ENSURING THAT IT REMAINS SECURE AND PROTECTED AT ALL TIMES. THIS DOCUMENT EXPLAINS OUR PRIVACY POLICY, AND HOW THE INFORMATION YOU TRANSFER TO ACTIVERIS SOFTWARE IS UTILIZED.

### How we collect information

We collect information from you including name, address, email address, etc. when you purchase or register Activeris Software programs and when you download a free trial/evaluation version. This information is used to verify transactions during use of Activeris Software programs or the Activeris Software website. Payment processing merchants utilized by Activeris Software and Activeris Software customers use the same careful privacy criteria as Activeris Software. The Activeris Software website is not intended for users under the age of 18, and Activeris Software does not intentionally gather information on users under the age of 18.

Activeris Software is not responsible for the information posted by users on public message boards, blogs, forums, etc., nor does Activeris Software supervise the potential use of this information by third-parties. Activeris Software makes no claims of privacy or confidentiality for items which users post in public spaces.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To improve customer service** (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 
  * **To process and confirm transactions** Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 
  * To contact you to confirm information provided
  * To complete your customer registration
  * To allow us to provide personalized content created around preferences, ideas, and suggestions provided 
  * To allow us to give early warnings for the termination of evaluation periods, or the continuation of evaluation periods, or early warnings for the termination of software licenses, or the continuation of software licenses. 

Activeris Software may release personal information at times when it is necessary to enforce our End User Licensing Agreement, Terms of Use, or other agreements (i.e.: to defend our intellectual property rights). These agreements can be found on the Activeris Software website and the End User Licensing Agreement can also be found within the software. Activeris Software may release or utilize your personal information when required by law, or when Activeris Software ascertains that relevant statutes and laws would require this release.”

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

#### Are external links provided?

Yes, Activeris Software may choose to include links to third-party websites. These websites may be related to Activeris Software and its partners, or may be unassociated websites but considered relevant. Any websites which Activeris Software links to are not covered by this Privacy Statement, and Activeris Software makes no claims or guarantees to the Privacy Statement, Terms, Conditions, etc. of external sites. Review each site's Privacy Policy for details on their own policies.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

Activeris Software cookies are primarily used to trace Activeris Software sales made by our affiliates and sales partners, to be certain that payments are made correctly, and accurate tracking information is provided with regard to Activeris Software sales.

Activeris Software cookies are for a time-restricted period, are under 5KB, are only visible to Activeris Software and contain no personal details. Activeris Software cookies contain time-limited ID numbers that are assigned to each computer that visits Activeris Software servers.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

#### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions documentation establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

#### Your Consent

By using the Activeris Software site or the Activeris Software program you consent to our online privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If our privacy policy is changed, this page will be accordingly updated and altered.
